Theodosius Dobzhansky Papers ca.1917-1975 Mss.B.D65
American Philosophical Society
- Series I: Correspondence, ca.1920-1975; 7.5 linear feet
  - Evolutionary Biology, 1967-1975; 19 folders (Box 5)
    - Folder 17, 1974-1975; 18 items (Box 5)
    - Folder 18, 1975; 19 items (Box 5)
    - Folder 19, 1975; 26 items (Box 5)
  - Ewan, Joseph, 1972; 2 items (Box 5)
  - Ewing, Arthur W., 1970; 2 items (Box 5)
  - Falek, Arthur, 1971; 1 item (Box 5)
  - Falk, Raphael, 1972; 2 items (Box 5)
  - Farber, Geraldine, 1971-1973; 2 items (Box 5)
  - Farber, Seymour M, 1971-1972; 4 items (Box 5)
  - Farmer, W. W., 1962; 1 item (Box 5)
  - Feldman, Jerry, 1971; 2 items (Box 5)
  - Félix Estrada, Rodolfo, 1961-1975; 2 folders (Box 5)
    Drosophila genetics; Population genetics; Publication; Travel -- Mexico
    - Folder 1, 1973, 1975; 9 items (Box 5)
    - Folder 2, 1975; 8 items (Box 5)
  - Fennell, Daniel J., 1970-1971; 4 items (Box 5)
  - Ferguson, Anthony, 1974; 2 items (Box 5)
  - Field, Andrew, 1970-1971; 2 items (Box 5)
  - Filipchenko, Yurii Aleksandrovich, 1927-1930; 4 folders (Box 5)
    Biographical and personal data; California Institute of Technology; Columbia University
    - Folder 1, 1929; 11 items (Box 5)
    - Folder 2, 1928; 13 items (Box 5)
    - Folder 3, 1928; 5 items (Box 5)
    - Folder 4, 1928; 9 items (Box 5)
  - Fisher, A. M., Jr., 1970; 5 items (Box 6)
  - Fisher, F. J. F., 1971; 4 items (Box 6)
  - Fisher, P. J., 1970; 2 items (Box 6)
  - Fisher, R. B., Jr., 1973; 3 items (Box 6)
  - Fitch, Walter M., 1970; 1 item (Box 6)
  - Fleming, Joyce Dudley, 1973; 2 items (Box 6)
  - Fontdenla, Antonio, 1974; 1 item (Box 6)
  - Forcey, Robert M., 1969; 1 item (Box 6)
  - Ford, C. E., 1971; 2 items (Box 6)
  - Ford, Donald C., 1972; 1 item (Box 6)
  - Ford, E. B., 1961-1975; 4 folders (Box 6)
    - Folder 1, 1961-1962; 10 items (Box 6)
    - Folder 2, 1970-1973; 28 items (Box 6)
    - Folder 3, 1974; 7 items (Box 6)
    - Folder 4, 1975; 11 items (Box 6)
  - FORGE (Fund of Overseas Research Grants and Education), 1970; 2 items (Box 6)
  - Fosberg, F. R., 1962; 1 item (Box 6)
  - Francoeur, Robert, 1970; 3 items (Box 6)
  - Frankel, Otto H., 1961-1962; 3 items (Box 6)
  - Franklin, Esther, 1974; 2 items (Box 6)
  - Franklin Institute, 1973-1974; 2 folders (Box 6)
    - Folder 1, 1973-1974; 4 items (Box 6)
    - Folder 2, 1973; 2 items (Box 6)
  - Fraser, Alexander S., 1962-1970; 5 items (Box 6)
  - Fraser, G. R., 1975; 2 items (Box 6)
  - Freeman, Derek, 1970-1972; 6 items (Box 6)
  - Freeman, W. H. and Company, 1975; 6 items (Box 6)
  - Freeman, Walter J., 1971; 2 items (Box 6)
  - French C. Stacy, 1971-1973; 4 items (Box 6)
  - Friedmann, Theodore, 1974; 2 items (Box 6)
  - Fromn, Robert, 1971; 2 items (Box 6)
  - Frota-Pessoa, 1961; 1 item (Box 6)
  - Fu, Jack, 1971; 2 items (Box 6)
  - Fugazy Travel Bureau, Inc., 1962; 1 item (Box 6)
  - Fuller, John L., 1972-1973; 2 items (Box 6)
  - Fundaçao Calouste Gulbenkian, 1972; 1 item (Box 6)
  - Futch, David G., 1972; 2 items (Box 6)
  - Futurology -- Geneva, 1975; 1 item (Box 6)
  - Gabrielian, Armen, 1970; 3 items (Box 6)
  - Galpersne, Ch., 1974; 1 item (Box 6)
  - Gaman, Barbara, 1969; 1 item (Box 6)
  - Ganesan, A. T., 1974; 2 items (Box 6)
  - Gantt, W. H., 1971; 2 items (Box 6)
  - Ganz, Aaron, 1962; 1 item (Box 6)
  - Garcia, John David, 1971-1972; 4 items (Box 6)
  - Gardelli, Raul N., 1970; 2 items (Box 6)
  - Garn, Stanley M., 1962-1970; 2 items (Box 6)
  - Garrelts, J. M., 1970; 2 items (Box 6)
  - Gasser, Herbert S., 1936; 1 item (Box 6)
  - Gause, G., 1970; 1 item (Box 6)
  - Gaustad, John E., 1972; 3 items (Box 6)
  - Geiger, H. H., 1973; 2 items (Box 6)
  - Genetic endowment and environment in the determination of behavior, 1971; 1 item (Box 6)
  - Genetics (periodical), 1962; 1 item (Box 6)
  - Genetics Society of America, n.d.; 1 item (Box 6)
  - Geneves, Santiago, 1970-1975; 5 items (Box 6)
  - Georgievsky, A. B., 1975; 4 items (Box 6)
  - Geren, Preston, ca.1972; 2 items (Box 6)
  - Gerking, Shelby, 1973; 1 item (Box 6)
  - Ghent, Arthur W., 1962-1972; 4 items (Box 6)
  - Gianni, Ernesto, 1972; 1 item (Box 6)
  - Gidari, Anthony S., 1970; 1 item (Box 6)
  - Giesel, James T., 1975; 1 item (Box 6)
  - Gilbert, G. M., 1971; 2 items (Box 6)
  - Gilbert, John J., 1975; 1 item (Box 6)
  - Gilbert, Larry, n.d.; 1 item (Box 6)
  - Giles, Norman H, 1972; 1 item (Box 6)
  - Gillham, Nicholas W., 1971; 2 items (Box 6)
  - Gillespie, E. C.
    See American Scientist (periodical)
  - Gillette, H. M.
    See Rockefeller Foundation
  - Gilmour, D. G., 1970; 2 items (Box 6)
  - Ginsberg, Benson E, 1972-1974; 2 items (Box 6)
  - Glade, Richard W., 1973; 1 item (Box 6)
  - Glass, Bentley, 1967-1972; 2 items (Box 6)
  - Globus, Gordon G., 1975; 2 items (Box 6)
  - Goddard, David R., 1975; 1 item (Box 6)
  - Goetz, Inge Steinvorth, 1970; 1 item (Box 6)
  - Gogeizel, E. P., n.d.; 3 items (Box 6)
  - Gola, Hannswerfter, 1971; 1 item (Box 6)
  - Gold, Albert
    See Rockefeller University
  - Goldberg, Ivan K, 1973; 2 items (Box 6)
  - Goldschmitt, Richard B., 1937-1940; 2 items (Box 6)
  - Golffing, Francis., 1962; 2 items (Box 6)
  - Goldbovsky, Mikail Davidovich, 1972-1974; 2 items (Box 6)
  - Goodall, Jane, 1972-1973; 9 items (Box 6)
  - Goodall, Varme, 1973-1974; 7 items (Box 6)
  - Goodfield, June, 1972; 1 item (Box 6)
  - Gordon, H. L. A., 1962; 2 items (Box 6)
  - Gorman, Teresa E., 1970; 2 items (Box 6)
  - Goswami, Usha, 1975; 2 items (Box 6)
  - Gottesman, I. I. (Irving I.), 1970-1971; 7 items (Box 6)
    Scientific organizations, meetings, programs; Shockley, William
  - Gottlieb, Frederick J., 1972; 1 item (Box 6)
  - Goudge, P. A., 1973; 1 item (Box 6)
  - Gough, Harrison, 1971-1972; 5 items (Box 6)
  - Gould, James A., 1971; 3 items (Box 6)
  - Gould, Stephen J., 1972; 2 items (Box 6)
  - Goy, Robert W., 1973-1975; 6 items (Box 6)
  - Gradmann, Hans, 1972; 2 items (Box 6)
  - Graham, Loren, 1971; 3 items (Box 6)
  - Grant, Peter R., 1975; 3 items (Box 6)
  - Grant, Verne, 1970-1975; 13 items (Box 6)
  - Grant, Vernon W., 1974; 1 item (Box 6)
  - Graubard, Stephen R., 1974; 3 items (Box 6)
  - Great Ideas Today, 1973-1974; 13 items (Box 6)
  - Grebecki, A., 1973; 2 items (Box 6)
  - Green, Christopher H., 1975; 2 items (Box 6)
  - Green, D. MacDonald, 1970; 4 items (Box 6)
  - Green, M. M. (Melvin Martin), 1970-1975; 6 items (Box 6)
    Astaurov, Boris L.; Drosophila genetics; Dubinin, Nikolai Petrovich; Russian politics and science; Timofeeff-Ressovsky, Nikolai W.; Travel -- Israel; Travel -- Russia; Travel -- Yugoslavia
  - Greene, John C., 1961-1969; 17 items (Box 6)
  - Greetings on 70th birthday, 1969; 6 folders (Box 6)
    Congratulations, greetings, thanks -- Dobzhansky, Theodosius. 70th birthday
    - Folder 1, 1969; 10 items (Box 6)
    - Folder 2, 1969; 20 items (Box 6)
    - Folder 3, 1969; 20 items (Box 6)
    - Folder 4, 1969; 18 items (Box 6)
    - Folder 5, 1969; 18 items (Box 6)
    - Folder 6, 1969; 17 items (Box 6)
  - Gregorovich, Andrew, 1972-1974; 1 item (Box 6)
  - Grekulinski, Edmund, 1971; 2 items (Box 6)
  - Grescitt, Lin, 1975; 1 item (Box 6)
  - Griffin, David, 1973-1974; 5 items (Box 6)
  - Griffin, Donald R, 1970; 4 items (Box 6)
  - Griggs, Robert F., 1933; 1 item (Box 6)
  - Grimes, John V., 1975; 4 items (Box 6)
  - Grimm, Robert H., 1970-1971; 5 items (Box 6)
  - Grizzell, L. Anthony, 1974; 2 items (Box 6)
  - Grobstein, Clifford, 1970; 1 item (Box 6)
  - Gross, Paul R., 1973; 3 items (Box 6)
  - Grossfield, Joseph, 1971-1973; 7 items (Box 6)
  - Grmek, M. D., 1969; 3 items (Box 6)
  - Guggenheim, John Simon, Memorial Foundation, 1970-1974; 4 items (Box 7)
  - Gupte, Anand P., 1 item (Box 7)
  - Gustafson, Perry, 1972-1974; 7 items (Box 7)
  - Gustafsson, Ake, 1969-1974; 5 items (Box 7)
    Biographical and personal data; Dubinin, Nikolai Petrovich; Lectures, public speaking; Russian politics and science; Timofeeff-Ressovsky, Nikolai W.; Travel -- Invitations, arrangements
  - Gutmann, James, 1973-1975; 16 items (Box 7)
  - Gwilliam, G. F., 1973; 2 items (Box 7)
  - Haag, John, 1973; 1 item (Box 7)
  - Haas, Peter, 1974; 1 item (Box 7)
  - Haber, A. H., 1975; 1 item (Box 7)
  - Haidemenakis, G. D., 1971; 1 item (Box 7)
  - Haldane, J. B. S., 1961; 3 items (Box 7)
  - Hall, Thomas, n.d.; 1 item (Box 7)
  - Halle, Louis J., 1974-1975; 6 items (Box 7)
  - Haller, John S., Jr., items (Box 7)
    Note: Item not found as of October 26, 2005
  - Halsey, A. H., 1962; 2 items (Box 7)
  - Hamburg, David A., 1961-1974; 20 items (Box 7)
  - Hamburger, Viktor, 1962; 2 items (Box 7)
  - Hamilton, Harold, 1975; 1 item (Box 7)
  - Hamilton, John M., 1972-1973; 4 items (Box 7)
  - Hanks, George D., 1971; 2 items (Box 7)
  - Hanna, Eric, 1975; 1 item (Box 7)
  - Hanson, Frank Blair, 1934-1935; 2 items (Box 7)
  - Harbury, Henry A., 1970; 3 items (Box 7)
  - Hardin, Garrett, 1971-1972; 2 items (Box 7)
  - Hardy, D. Elmo, 1973; 2 items (Box 7)
  - Harland, S. C., 1933; 1 item (Box 7)
  - Harm, Walter, 1972; 1 item (Box 7)
  - Harmon, N. Paul, 1962; 1 item (Box 7)
  - Harper and Row, Publishers, 1970; 2 items (Box 7)
  - Harris, Tom M., 1962; 1 item (Box 7)
  - Harrison, G. Ainsworth, 1970-1975; 9 items (Box 7)
  - Hart, Benjamin L., 1975; 4 items (Box 7)
  - Harvard University, 1962; 1 item (Box 7)
  - Harvard University Prather Lectures in Biology, n.d.; 1 item (Box 7)
  - Harvard University Press, 1961-1962; 5 items (Box 7)
  - Haskins, Caryl P., 1963-1974; 5 items (Box 7)
  - Hatch, Melville H., 1934; 1 item (Box 7)
  - Haury, Emil W., 1973; 3 items (Box 7)
  - Havender, William R., 1963-1975; 2 folders (Box 7)
    Behavioral genetics, IQ; Jensen, Arthur Robert; Publication
    - Folder 1, 1963-1975; 2 items (Box 7)
    - Folder 2, 1975; 3 items (Box 7)
  - Hawkins, Tom, 1972; 1 item (Box 7)
  - Hays, James D., 1971-1972; 6 items (Box 7)
  - Heath, Barbara, Honeyman, 1971; 1 item (Box 7)
  - Heberer, Gerhard, 1962-1971; 2 items (Box 7)
  - Hecht, Max K., 1970-1972; 9 items (Box 7)
  - Hecht, Stephen T., 1975; 2 items (Box 7)
  - Heed, William B., 1969-1973; 4 items (Box 7)
  - Heese, Wolfgang, 1973-1975; 3 items (Box 7)
  - Hefner, Philip, 1970; 2 items (Box 7)
  - Heim, Werner G., 1972-1973; 8 items (Box 7)
  - Hellenistic Society for Humanistic Studies. First International Symposium, Delphi, 1969; 2 items (Box 7)
  - Henderson, Thomas Bain, 1973; 1 item (Box 7)
  - Herrmann, Heinz, 1971; 1 item (Box 7)
  - Hertz, Karl, 1970; 3 items (Box 7)
  - Hiorns, Robert W., 1975; 2 items (Box 7)
  - Hirsch, Jerry, 1961; 4 items (Box 7)
    Behavioral genetics, IQ; Graduate study -- Kessler, Seymour; Population genetics; Scientific organizations, meetings, programs
  - Hitch, Charles Johnston, 1975; 1 item (Box 7)
  - Hoagland, Hudson, 1971-1975; 3 items (Box 7)
  - Hobey, William D., 1972; 2 items (Box 7)
  - Hochstein, Lawrence I., 1974; 1 item (Box 7)
  - Hocking, B., 1970-1971; 9 items (Box 7)
  - Hodge, Ruth Patrick, 1970-1975; 4 items (Box 7)
  - Hodgson, Edward S., 1969-1971; 4 items (Box 7)
  - Hoenigsberg, Hugo F., 1970-1971; 8 items (Box 7)
  - Hollaender, Alexander, 1974; 2 items (Box 7)
  - Hollencamp, Charles, 1973; 2 items (Box 7)
  - Holt, John V. van, Jr., 1961; 1 item (Box 7)
  - Holt, Rinehart and Winston, Inc, 1970-1971; 2 items (Box 7)
  - Hook, Ernest B., 1974; 4 items (Box 7)
  - Hook, James, 1974; 2 items (Box 7)
  - Horowitz, Norman H., 1974; 2 items (Box 7)
  - Horseman, H. G., 1972; 1 item (Box 7)
  - Houghton Mifflin Company, 1971; 2 items (Box 7)
  - Howells, William White, 1970-1971; 3 items (Box 7)
  - Hubby, John L., 1972; 1 item (Box 7)
  - Huether, Carl A., 1970; 2 items (Box 7)
  - Huffman, Donald M., 1969-1975; 6 items (Box 7)
  - Hulse, Frederick S., 1971; 1 item (Box 7)
  - Human Biology (Journal), 1975; 1 item (Box 7)
  - Hume, John C., 1971; 2 items (Box 7)
  - Hunter, Alice S., 1968-1975; 14 items (Box 7)
  - Hunziker, Juan H., 1969-1970; 3 items (Box 7)
  - Hutchison, Victor H., 1974; 1 item (Box 7)
  - Huxley, Julian S., 1938; 1 item (Box 7)
  - Imai, Midori, 1972-1975; 8 items (Box 7)
  - Inamdar, N. B., 1970; 1 item (Box 7)
  - Ingle, Dwight J., 1972; 3 items (Box 7)
  - Institute for the study of Man in Africa, 1975; 4 items (Box 7)
  - Institute of Society, Ethics, and the Life Sciences, 1971-1974; 8 items (Box 7)
  - International Association for Social Psychiatry, 1973; 2 items (Box 7)
  - International Education Board, 1927; 6 items (Box 7)
  - International Science Foundation, 1970; 2 items (Box 7)
  - Invitations, 1964; 13 items (Box 7)
  - Isik, Kani, 1975; 2 items (Box 7)
  - Ives, Philip T., ca.1970; 5 items (Box 7)
  - Jackson, Ides, 1972; 1 item (Box 7)
  - Jacquard, A., 1975; 2 items (Box 7)
  - Jain, Subodh K., 1970; 1 item (Box 7)
  - Jameson, David L., 1972-1974; 10 items (Box 7)
  - Jayakar, S. D., 1974; 2 items (Box 7)
  - Jeffery, Duane E., 1971-1975; 5 items (Box 7)
  - Jenkins, Iredell, 1962; 1 item (Box 7)
  - Jensen, Arthur Robert, 1972-1975; 2 folders (Box 7)
    Behavioral genetics, IQ; Human genetics -- Race; Invitations; Population genetics
    - Folder 1, 1972-1973; 7 items (Box 7)
    - Folder 2, 1973-1974; 10 items (Box 7)
  - Jensen, Tove S., 1975; 3 items (Box 7)
  - Jha, A. P., 1970-1975; 20 items (Box 7)
  - Joenike, John R., 1972; 1 item (Box 7)
  - John, Kenneth R., 1962; 1 item (Box 7)
  - Johnson, Ebba, 1974; 1 item (Box 7)
  - Johnson, Frank M., 1974; 1 item (Box 7)
  - Johnson, George B., 1971; 4 items (Box 7)
  - Johnston, Shirley, 1973; 2 items (Box 7)
  - Jones, Larry W., 1973; 1 item (Box 7)
  - Jones, Robert D., 1973; 2 items (Box 7)
  - Jones, Roger, 1975; 1 item (Box 7)
  - Joravsky, David, 1961; 1 item (Box 7)
  - Journal Club, n.d.; 1 item (Box 7)
  - Journal of Heredity (periodical), 1962-1975; 13 items (Box 7)
  - Journal of Human Evolution, 1970; 2 items (Box 7)
  - Journal of Molecular, Cellular and Behavioral Origins and Evolution, 1975; 2 items (Box 7)
  - Judd, Burke H., 1970; 6 items (Box 7)
  - Jukes, Thomas H., 1969-1975; 17 items (Box 7)
    Biochemistry and organic chemistry; Evolution; Molecular genetics; Poetry and literature; Publication; Russian politics and science -- Lysenko, Trofim Denisovich; Russian politics and science -- Medvedev, Zhores A.; Teaching
  - Kadushin, Charles, 1970; 1 item (Box 8)
  - Kalamazoo College, 1966; 2 items (Box 8)
  - Kale, P. G., 1970; 2 items (Box 8)
  - Kalmus H., 1969; 1 item (Box 8)
  - Kambysellis, Michael P., 1970; 1 item (Box 8)
  - Kanaev, 1969-1974; 6 items (Box 8)
  - Kaplan, Arnold R., 1971; 2 items (Box 8)
  - Karavaev, V., 1935; 2 items (Box 8)
  - Kareev, Georgi, 1928; 1 item (Box 8)
  - Karkalas, Elias, 1970; 2 items (Box 8)
  - Karlin, Samuel, 1975; 1 item (Box 8)
  - Karolyi, L. V., 1970; 2 items (Box 8)
  - Karpechenko, G. D., 1921; 1 item (Box 8)
  - Kass, Leon, 1971-1973; 6 items (Box 8)
  - Kastritsis, Costas D., 1970-1973; 17 items (Box 8)
    Biographical and personal data; Cytogenetics; Evolution; Political issues -- Greece; Population genetics; Publication; Recommendations; University of Texas; University of Thessaloniki
  - Katz, Solomon H., 1973; 2 items (Box 8)
  - Kenefick, D. G., 1975; 1 item (Box 8)
  - Kennedy, Joseph P, Jr., Foundation, 1971-1973; 17 items (Box 8)
  - Kerkis, Julius J., 1920-1975; 4 folders (Box 8)
    Biographical and personal data; Drosophila genetics; Russian politics and science
    - Folder 1, 1920-1930; 27 items (Box 8)
    - Folder 2, 1930-1931; 19 items (Box 8)
    - Folder 3, 1969-1972; 19 items (Box 8)
    - Folder 4, 1973-1975; 17 items (Box 8)
  - Kernaghan, R. Peter, 1971-1973; 5 items (Box 8)
  - Kerr, Warwick Estevam, 1970-1975; 13 items (Box 8)
  - Kershner, John R., 1972-1973; 2 items (Box 8)
  - Kessler, Seymour, 1972-1973; 2 items (Box 8)
  - Kettlewell, H. B. D., 1970-1975; 3 items (Box 8)
  - Keyes, Frederick W., 1971; 2 items (Box 8)
  - Keys, Donald F., 1973; 3 items (Box 8)
  - Khailov, K. M., 1970-1974; 9 items (Box 8)
  - Kidwell, James F., 1971; 1 item (Box 8)
  - Kihara, H., 1970; 2 items (Box 8)
  - Kimball, R. F., 1971; 1 item (Box 8)
  - Kimball Makielski, Sally, 1970; 2 items (Box 8)
  - King, Charles E., 1972; 2 items (Box 8)
  - King, Jack Lester, 1970-1976; 2 folders (Box 8)
    Ethical issues; Evolution; Population genetics; Research support; Teaching -- Evolution
    - Folder 1, 1970-1974; 22 items (Box 8)
    - Folder 2, 1973-1976; 2 items (Box 8)
  - King, James R., 1972; 3 items (Box 8)
  - King, Robert C., 1971-1975; 2 folders (Box 8)
    Population genetics; Publication
    - Folder 1, 1971-1975; 9 items (Box 8)
    - Folder 2, 1973; 1 item (Box 8)
  - Kinsey, Alfred C., 1936; 1 item (Box 8)
  - Kirichenko, A. N., 1935; 1 item (Box 8)
  - Kirk, Dudley, 1973; 1 item (Box 8)
  - Kirpichnikov, V., 1972-1974; 1 item (Box 8)
  - Kitagawa, Osamu, 1969-1971; 8 items (Box 8)
  - Kitzmiller, James B., 1972-1974; 3 items (Box 8)
  - Klavins, John V., 1973; 2 items (Box 8)
  - Klein, Richard M., 1971; 1 item (Box 8)
  - Knapp, Byron H., 1970; 2 items (Box 8)
  - Kochanski, 1969; 1 item (Box 8)
  - Koffler, Henry, 1972; 1 item (Box 8)
  - Kohler, Richard C., 1973; 2 items (Box 8)
  - Kojima, Ken-ichi, 1970-1971; 5 items (Box 8)
  - Koller, Pius Charles, 1939-1972; 4 items (Box 8)
  - Kon, Mark A., n.d.; 1 item (Box 8)
  - Koref-Santibañez, Susi, 1970-1974; 14 items (Box 8)
    Biographical and personal data; Fellowships, assistantships; Political issues -- Chile; Population genetics; Travel -- Invitations, arrangements
  - Korneev, Sergei G., 1963; 1 item (Box 8)
  - Kraft, R Wayne, 1972; 1 item (Box 8)
  - Kreutzer, Richard D., 1974; 2 items (Box 8)
  - Knapp, W., 1975; 1 item (Box 8)
  - Krier, Timothy V., 1972; 1 item (Box 8)
  - Krimbas, Costas B., 1970-1975; 11 items (Box 8)
    Biographical and personal data; Conferences and symposia; Crow, James F.; Drosophila genetics; Kimura, Motoo; Mouse genetics; Population genetics; Publication; Publication -- Genetics; Teaching -- Harvard University; Travel -- Invitations, arrangements; Unpublished manuscripts, notes, etc.
  - Krimbas, Costas B. and Spyros Tsakas: The Genetics of Dacus oleae, ca.1969; 1 item (Box 8)
  - Kristiansen, Kristian, ca.1957; 1 item (Box 8)
  - Kristof, Ladis K. D., 1973; 1 item (Box 8)
  - Krízenecky, Jaroslav, 1961; 1 item (Box 8)
  - Kühn, Alfred, 1961; 1 item (Box 8)
  - Kuhn, Barbara A., n.d.; 2 items (Box 8)
  - Kumamoto, Junji, 1972; 2 items (Box 8)
  - Kunicki-Goldfinger, Weadyseaw, 1974; 3 items (Box 8)
  - Kurth, G., 1975; 3 items (Box 8)
  - Kuspira, J., 1971; 2 items (Box 8)
  - Kuznicki, L., items (Box 8)
  - Kvenvolden, Keith A., 1974; 2 items (Box 8)
  - Lämmel, E., 1975; 1 item (Box 8)
  - Lakhotia, S. C., 1972; 2 items (Box 8)
  - Lakovaara, Seppo, 1970-1975; 7 items (Box 8)
  - Lamotte, Maxime, 1969-1974; 5 items (Box 8)
  - Lanchester, Horace, 1936; 1 item (Box 8)
  - Land, Barbara, 1970-1973; 16 items (Box 8)
  - Landauer, Walter, 1936; 1 item (Box 8)
  - Landers, Milton H., 1973; 2 items (Box 8)
  - Landis, Bernard, 1970-1971; 5 items (Box 8)
  - Lang, Anton, 1970; 3 items (Box 8)
  - Laszlo, Ervin, 1970-1971; 9 items (Box 8)
  - Laughlin, William S., 1974; 4 items (Box 8)
  - Lavocat R., 1973; 2 items (Box 8)
  - Lawless, James G., 1974; 2 items (Box 8)
  - Layzer, David, 1973-1975; 3 items (Box 8)
  - Leake, Chauncey, 1972; 1 item (Box 8)
  - Leakey, L. S. B. Foundation, 1973; 2 items (Box 8)
  - Leakey, R. E., 1971; 1 item (Box 8)
  - Lédoux, Andrée, 1971; 2 items (Box 8)
  - Lee, Philip Randolph, 1971; 1 item (Box 8)
  - Leikola, Anto, 1971; 1 item (Box 8)
  - Leitner, Philip, 1970; 1 item (Box 8)
  - Lejeune, Jérome, 1970; 1 item (Box 8)
  - Le Manse, G., 1974; 1 item (Box 8)
  - Leopoldina Deutsche Akademie der Naturforacher, 1970-1975; 4 items (Box 8)
  - Lepin, T. K., 1931; 1 item (Box 8)
  - Lerner, I. Michael (Isadore Michael), 1970-1975; 4 folders (Box 8)
    Behavioral genetics, IQ; Biographical and personal data -- Timofeeff-Ressovsky, Nikolai W.; National Academy of Sciences -- Shockley, William; Russian politics and science -- Medvedev, Zhores A.
    - Folder 1, 1970; 19 items (Box 8)
    - Folder 2, 1970; 12 items (Box 8)
    - Folder 3, 1970-1973; 14 items (Box 8)
    - Folder 4, 1973; 14 items (Box 8)
  - Lestina, Letitia, 1975; 6 items (Box 8)
  - Levene, Howard, 1971; 1 item (Box 9)
  - Levey, David, 1975; 3 items (Box 9)
  - Levin, Donald A., 1972-1974; 5 items (Box 9)
  - Levine, Louis, 1973-1975; 12 items (Box 9)
    Drosophila genetics -- Mexico; Photographs; Population genetics; Publication
  - Levins, Richard, 1974; 2 items (Box 9)
  - Levit, M. M. (Mikhail M.), 1930-1935; 4 items (Box 9)
    Genetics; Russian politics and science
  - Levitan, Max, 1970-1971; 3 items (Box 9)
  - Levizky, G., 1930; 1 item (Box 9)
  - Lewis, E. B., 1974; 1 item (Box 9)
  - Lewis, Harlan, 1972-1973; 4 items (Box 9)
  - Lewontin, R. C. (Richard Charles), 1961-1975; 3 folders (Box 9)
    Behavioral genetics, IQ; Ethical issues; National Academy of Sciences; Political issues; Population genetics; Powell, Jeffrey R.; Publication
    - Folder 1, 1961-1970; 15 items (Box 9)
    - Folder 2, 1971-1973; 17 items (Box 9)
    - Folder 3, 1974-1975; 14 items (Box 9)
  - Li, C. C., 1970; 1 item (Box 9)
  - Life (magazine), 1970; 2 items (Box 9)
  - Lindzey, Gardner, 1971-1972; 6 items (Box 9)
  - Lippincott, William H., 1970-1972; 10 items (Box 9)
  - Ljubishev, 1971; 1 item (Box 9)
  - Loehlin, John C., 1972-1973; 3 items (Box 9)
  - Löther, Rolf, n.d.; 1 item (Box 9)
  - Loewenberg, Bert James, 1970-1971; 4 items (Box 9)
  - Lofstrom, Bdward V., 1970; 4 items (Box 9)
  - Losada, Lewis David, 1973; 1 item (Box 9)
  - Lowe, Charles H., 1970; 1 item (Box 9)
  - Lower, William R., 1970-1975; 5 items (Box 9)
  - Lowrey, George H, 1973; 1 item (Box 9)
  - Ludwig, Robert, 1972; 1 item (Box 9)
  - Luhmann, Dianne, 1975; 2 items (Box 9)
  - Lundgren, D. G., 1968-1970; 3 items (Box 9)
  - Luria, Salvador E., 1970-1973; 7 items (Box 9)
  - Luria, Salvador E. Organic Biology, 1969-1970; 8 items (Box 9)
  - McClearn, Gerald E., 1970-1972; 3 items (Box 9)
  - McCord, James I., 1971; 2 items (Box 9)
  - McDowell, Rebecca E., 1975; 2 items (Box 9)
  - MacFadyen, A., 1970; 2 items (Box 9)
  - McGill, Susan, 1970; 1 item (Box 9)
  - McGreath, John C., 1970; 2 items (Box 9)
  - McGraw-Hill Book Company, 1970-1972; 6 items (Box 9)
  - Machado, C. E., 1975; 2 items (Box 9)
  - McKusick, Victor A., 1969-1970; 2 items (Box 9)
  - McLachlan, Gordon A., 1974; 2 items (Box 9)
  - McLean, Donald D., 1974; 1 item (Box 9)
  - MacMillen, Richard, 1972; 1 item (Box 9)
  - McNally, J. O., 1971; 3 items (Box 9)
  - McWhirter, Kennedy, 1972; 1 item (Box 9)
  - Madden, Ward, 1970-1971; 13 items (Box 9)
  - Maharishi European Research University, 1975; items (Box 9)
  - Mai Larry L., 1975; 5 items (Box 9)
  - Maillet, 1975; 1 item (Box 9)
  - Mainardi, Danilo, 1974; 1 item (Box 9)
  - Malik, Kausar Sultana, 1973; 2 items (Box 9)
  - Mallis, Donald, 1971; 2 items (Box 9)
  - Malogolowkin-Cohen, Chana, 1970-1975; 3 folders (Box 9)
    Biographical and personal data; Population genetics; Research support
    - Folder 1, 1970-1974; 6 items (Box 9)
    - Folder 2, 1974; 15 items (Box 9)
    - Folder 3, 1975; 13 items (Box 9)
  - Man in the light of evolutionary biology, Lecture II-V, ca.1970; 1 item (Box 9)
  - Man in the light of evolutionary biology, Lecture III, ca.1970; 1 item (Box 9)
  - Man in the light of evolutionary biology, Lecture IV, ca.1970; 1 item (Box 9)
  - Man in the light of evolutionary biology, Lecture V, ca.1970; 1 item (Box 9)
  - Mandel, David, 1973-1975; 8 items (Box 9)
  - Mankato State College, 1973; 2 items (Box 9)
  - Manwell, Clyde, 1970; 1 item (Box 9)
  - Margen, Sheldon, 1975; 2 items (Box 9)
  - Margenau, Henry, 1913; items (Box 9)
  - Margulis, Lynn, 1973; 2 items (Box 9)
  - Marinkovic, Dragoslav, 1970-1975; 13 items (Box 9)
  - Markert, Clement L, 1971; 2 items (Box 9)